Retail Store Employees Union Local 345 (Rochester, NY) Photographs 5823 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Retail Store Employees Union Local 345 (Rochester, NY) Photographs
1964-1981
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Retail Store Employees Union. Local 345
5823 P
2.28 cubic feet
2.3 linear ft.
Photographs.
Retail Store Employees Union Local 345 (Rochester, NY) Photographs including photos from the City of Rochester, Union Label Week, seminar dinners, union parties, picket lines and miscellaneous activities the union has participated in.
8507489
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 30, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 17, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5823: Retail Store Employees Union Local 345 (Rochester, NY) Records
Retail Store Employees Union; Retail Store Employees Union. Local 345 (Rochester, N.Y.)
8507489
- City of Rochester - Union Label Week 9/7-9/12/1981 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Steward Seminar Dinner (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Union Label 1973 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Stewards Seminar (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Union Label & Steward Seminars - Misc. (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Misc. Photos (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Toys for Tots Dance (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Toys for Tots (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Union Label Convention - Syracuse, NY (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Two Guys Employees on strike (Box 1, Folder 10)
- GHANA Session at Seminar (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Misc. Photos (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Christmas, New Years Meeting/Dinner (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Misc. Photos (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Two Guys Strike (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Active Ballot Club (ABC) (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Union Label (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Syracuse Dance 1966 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Local 345 Photo album (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Assorted photos of picket lines (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Assorted photos of picket lines (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Assorted photos of picket lines (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Assorted photos of picket lines (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Assorted photos of picket lines (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Assorted photos of picket lines (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Assorted photos of picket lines (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Assorted photos of picket lines (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Assorted photos of picket lines (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Assorted photos of picket lines (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Assorted photos of picket lines (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Assorted photos of picket lines (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Assorted photos of picket lines (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Assorted photos of picket lines (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Assorted photos of picket lines (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Assorted photos of picket lines (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Assorted photos of picket lines (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Assorted photos of picket lines (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Assorted photos of picket lines (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Assorted photos of picket lines (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Assorted photos of picket lines (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Assorted photos of picket lines (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Assorted photos of picket lines (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Misc. Photos (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Misc. Photos (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Misc. Photos (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Misc. Photos (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Misc. Photos (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Misc. Photos (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Misc. Photos (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Misc. Photos (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Misc. Photos (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Misc. Photos (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Misc. Photos (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Misc. Photos (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Misc. Photos (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Misc. Photos (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Misc. Photos (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Misc. Photos (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Misc. Photos (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Retail Clerks International Association, Certificate of Achievement, Local 345, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- 2 Portrait photographs of unknown men (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Retail Clerks International Association - 1964 Leadership Institute - Sept. 4, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  panoramic photo
- Active Ballot Club Conference - September 27, 1968 - Washington, D.C. (Box 5, Folder 2)
- RCIA Inaugural - Washington, D.C. - September 28, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Retail Clerks International Association - Active Ballot Club - May 1-2, 1970 - Washington, D.C. (Box 5, Folder 4)